Number one
K-content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM IS
NOT SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS PRODUCT PLACEMENTS
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
THIS DRAMA
IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION
ANY ADVICE FOR YOUNGER DESIGNERS
OR THOSE FINDING THEIR WAY?
DON'T TRY TOO HARD TO CHANGE YOURSELF
CHANGE WHERE YOU ARE
Mr. Kang.
Yes?
What do you think
about me applying
for that expat position to Paris?
I was just asking.
I'm already learning a lot right now
but I was wondering what it'd be like
to be somewhere completely new.
I think it's a great idea.
- Do you mean it?
- Of course.
It's important to learn
in a different environment.
And an employee's growth
is an advantage to the business.
Give it a go.
What about you?
Me?
Are you okay with it?
Of course.
The flight to Paris
isn't that long anyway.
What? Hey.
Why would you go there?
You just started dating
for the first time.
What did he say?
What do you think?
He must be shocked and scared.
He said he's fine with it.
- What?
He told me to go to Paris.
Wait, maybe he was too flustered.
He seemed to mean it.
Hey, let me tell you this
because I've been there.
Long-distance relationships
never work out.
- Why?
- Your boyfriend
is someone even CEO Han Jeong-yeon
wanted to date.
Women won't let him be alone
during that long period.
- They'll snatch him right away.
- What?
Yes, you said there were
more than a couple of women
who asked him out at work.
LET'S SNATCH KANG HA-GI RIGHT AWAY
- Kang Ha-gi!
No way.
No matter how I think about it,
it can't happen.
I love you, Da-reum.
I love you, too.
- Hey!
- My goodness!
What's taking you so long?
I'm hungry.
You've been
frying those dumplings all day long.
Why, that...
Yes.
Wow, you've burned them all.
So why did you tell her to go
if you didn't even mean it?
It's so hot.
Listen up.
Dating is like a fried dumpling.
When it gets hot, flip it over.
When you want to cool it,
put it down.
You need a bit of distance
to stay together even longer.
You're taking a step back
to take two steps forward later.
That's what real players do.
Why did it have to be France?
People there greet each other
with a kiss on the cheek.
- I don't like it.
- Are you anxious already?
- I'm not.
- You're scared.
Just be cool and let Da-reum go.
Don't be so lame.
If you go, that'll be the end of it.
You two will break up for sure.
Let her go
so you can be together longer.
Be cool about it and let her go.
It's a go!
You cannot go. It's a no!
- Go!
- No!
FINAL EPISODE
CEO KANG HA-GI
Come in.
Mr. Kang.
Have you seen the notice
HAN sent today?
No, not yet.
It was about our expat employee.
"If possible, we'd like to have
Ms. Nam Da-reum sent here."
That's what it says.
REQUESTING EXPAT EMPLOYEE FROM KOREA
STATIONED AT:
MAISON HAN PARIS HEADQUARTERS
REQUESTED EMPLOYEE:
NAM DA-REUM
I haven't checked
with Ms. Da-reum yet.
- Please do.
- Sorry?
Tell them that we'll consider
the request favorably
if she wishes to go.
- Favorably?
- Yes.
It's a great opportunity.
The employee's growth leads
to the company's growth.
It's growth for everyone.
GROWTH FOR EVERYONE
Mr. Kang.
- Are you sure about this?
- Yes, of course.
All right, then.
KIM MIN-WOO
Hey, I just saw
Mr. Choi Seong-wook here.
HAND CAR WASH
It'll take you forever
to wash all three cars.
Move it, will you?
Did you get this part?
You didn't get the wheels.
Get to it already.
- Choi.
- Yes?
Don't just wipe the sides.
Get the roof too.
Yes, sir.
- Don't slack off. Wipe it harder.
- Yes, sir.
You left to do this job?
Why did you do it
when you didn't even make a big haul?
Right? Tell me about it.
Why didn't you send them
the final version?
Because I'm an idiot.
I couldn't bear
to see you go down.
Do you remember?
When we first got
an office for Appello
we carried boxes
all throughout the night.
Whenever the server crashed
we'd spend days
practically living there.
So how could I
forget all that?
I got some relief
after doing that awful thing.
But my heart hit rock bottom.
I didn't know what got into me.
This is for the better.
No one's going to understand that.
You should've stabbed my back
and gotten good money for it.
I still...
despise you so much.
Yes, that's only fair.
Ha-gi.
It's not your fault
that I've become broken.
It's not because you succeeded.
It's just that...
Instead of cheering you on
I hated myself for feeling so petty.
And I couldn't deal with it.
I'm sorry. I mean it.
And thanks
for giving me a chance
to make an excuse.
Hey, Choi. We're busy over here!
Yes, coming!
Hey, Ha-gi.
I'll always be...
grateful for you, man.
I have to go.
OVERSEAS ASSIGNMENT APPLICATION
ASSIGNED TO:
MAISON HAN PARIS HEADQUARTERS
I thought you'd be thrilled.
What's wrong? Is it Mr. Kang?
He's already having a tough time
because of Mr. Choi.
I didn't want to add to that.
Well, I guess
the timing is a bit off.
Will you be okay...
giving up on this?
You should give serious thought
about what you really want.
Seong-wook said
he hated himself
for having awful feelings
for someone
he should be showing support to.
It hit close to home.
I know it's a great opportunity
for Ms. Da-reum.
But I want her to stay.
I find myself so pathetic.
By now, I should be
used to saying goodbye...
to people.
But it's too hard.
Then cling to her.
Okay?
If I did that
because I couldn't handle it
it would kill her dream too.
Wow.
I should let her go.
That's the right thing to do.
I really can't deal with you.
Hey, be careful.
Hey, man. Pull it together.
Kang Ha-gi.
Hey, I'm fine.
I'm totally fine.
Let's go for round two.
To my place!
You have to give her
your drunken honesty
- instead of looking wasted.
- Excellent.
On my way.
- My drunken confession!
- Okay.
- On my way!
- Mr. Kang.
Mr. Kang.
- Are you okay?
- It's Ms. Da-reum.
It's me.
- Ms. Da-reum.
- Yes?
Ms. Da-reum.
You're so cute.
You're way too cute, my dear Da-reum.
So you're drunk.
How do I let you go
when you're so cute?
Kiss me.
Have you lost your mind?
Go do that at home.
Mr. Kang.
Are you okay?
I've never seen him so wasted before.
Let's take him back home for now.
- One, two, three.
- Are you okay?
- Someone hit me.
- No one did. Let's go.
- No.
Why did you drink so much?
You can go too.
- I'm fine, really.
- Where are you telling me to go?
Sit down for a minute.
Mr. Kang?
Mr. Kang.
Don't go.
Don't go, Da-reum.
He's not cool with it.
He just doesn't want
to get in your way.
CONTACT SOLUTION, Q-TIPS
TRAVEL PILLOW, BLANKET,
PAIN RELIEF PATCHES, RAMYEON
OUR BELOVED
PARIS, FRANCE
SUPPLIES FOR PARIS
BAND-AID, OINTMENT, INSTANT SOUP
Should we do these
for Olivier's new colors?
It's too light.
Wasn't there a jacket?
Like this one.
Ms. Da-reum took the day off.
Today was the deadline to apply
to work abroad, and she didn't apply.
SPICY CHICKEN, ANGUK BRANCH
8,530 WON, ACCEPT
QUICK DELIVERY
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR, FIVE
LET'S GO
- D.N.X.
MUSIC WAVE
- One.
- Two.
- Three.
- Four.
Five. Let's go!
- Let's go!
ONE, TWO,
THREE, FOUR
FIVE, LET'S GO
I feel so much more relieved
after deciding not to go.
I mean, Paris isn't a big deal.
Here, I got my friends, Appello...
No matter how hard things get
don't let go of my hand.
Okay.
...and Mr. Kang.
Okay, Nam Da-reum.
You made a great decision.
How sweet.
You're alive.
Chan.
I should've been there by your side.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
I let go of your hand.
You didn't.
I'm the one who ran away.
Jeez. You must've been
the most frightened.
But I must've been young too
because I ran away like you.
Let us...
stop running away.
Come back, Roy.
Do you think
the other guys will accept me?
They talk crap about you
when your part comes on at practice.
They pretend like
they hate you so much
yet they wait.
Did you see the ad?
That's how we all feel.
CEO KANG HA-GI OF APPELLO
You know the application
is due today, right?
I'll wait until you come.
YOU KNOW THE APPLICATION
IS DUE TODAY, RIGHT?
I'LL WAIT UNTIL YOU COME
Ms. Da-reum.
Have you really been waiting for me?
Yes.
You didn't turn in the application...
and you made me worry all day.
You kept pretending
like you were cool with it too.
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
I'm the expert at acting fine.
Is that why you ran away?
No.
Working with you
eating with you
and staying by your side
on days when we have nothing to do
were what I loved.
So I wanted to keep being with you.
Ms. Da-reum.
If I must choose one or the other...
I choose you.
You're right.
I didn't want you to go.
I thought this could mean
goodbye forever
so I got anxious.
But what beat my anxiety...
must be my love for you.
What I hated more was the idea
of you not going because of me.
When you talked about Paris
your eyes dazzled so brightly.
It was the face...
I fell in love with.
A face full of excitement
and happiness.
I hope to see you...
always looking like that.
Don't worry about me and go.
See and experience
as much as you can.
So that you can do an even better job
at what you want to do, okay?
Even if I leave...
you won't let go, will you?
Of course not.
We'd be holding each other
more tightly.
Let us
trust each other.
Okay?
Congratulations, Da-reum.
I mean, Paris? That's so cool.
Upload lots of pictures
in the group chat, okay?
And you have to come back.
Yes, I'll make sure
I check in with you.
- Cheers.
Wait, you can't do that without me.
Let me do it too.
- Cheers.
Are you ready to go?
I have something to share with you.
Oh my gosh. Mr. Kang.
Actually...
Ms. Da-reum and I are...
We know, Mr. Kang.
Wow, congratulations.
- Congrats.
- Good for you.
- Finally.
- It was about time.
I wasn't done talking.
Do you know how tiring it was
to pretend like we didn't know?
- Tell me about it. It was tiring.
- So exhausting.
It was fun to see your awful acting.
We won't be able to hold
the rookies' meet-up for a while.
Right?
It was mostly the two of us, anyway.
I need cola.
Hey, give me some soda.
That wrong message in the chat...
Mr. Kang.
- One, two, three, four.
- Five, six, seven, eight.
- Two, two, three, four...
- Wait.
Chan, you stepped out
half a beat too early.
No, I stepped out at "two, two."
You got out at "two."
You were both rushing.
- Hey.
- You were both wrong, so get back.
- Hey, Teo.
- Fine. I was wrong. Do it over.
You know how it goes.
This isn't it. Hurry up.
You're here.
I'm a bit late, aren't I?
I've been waiting for so long.
- I missed you, kid.
- Me too.
- Let me see our baby's face.
- Have you all been well?
What did you go through?
You're a mess for a K-pop idol.
- You're right.
- He looks way better than you guys.
What are you talking about?
- What took you so long?
APPELLO CLOSED
COLLEGEIST POP-UP IS OVER, THANK YOU
Can you play this song?
YOU
DEMO VERSION
What do you think?
I love it.
That's it?
It feels weird.
You may be saying it to your fans
but it's what I wanted to say to you.
So you're saying
it's a pass?
We both held out
for quite a long time.
Hey, that's...
This is the exact shape
that my all-time favorite celebrity
always draws
when he signs autographs.
Today is my birthday
so I want to buy it for myself
as a gift.
Excuse me. Happy birthday.
It was me.
I gave you that pendant
on your birthday.
And because you had kept it all along
I found the courage
to get back on stage.
I also endured life,
believing that it was from you.
I think...
I figured out
what it is that I want to do.
Just as I was happy as your fan
I also want to do something
that'll awaken passion
in people's hearts.
Is that why you're going to Paris?
Yes.
I don't know
if I can pull it off, though.
I'm sure you will.
I've seen
how serious you are about this.
I was happy to have someone
so wonderful as my fan.
Now, it's your turn
to do what makes your heart race.
Passport.
Here.
The guidebook.
Emergency medicine.
You basically bought me a pharmacy.
Are you sure it's enough?
I'm not going to Paris
to sell medicine.
I just don't want you to get sick.
I think I got everything, right?
That's our knot.
You attached it there.
I'm taking this with me.
So it'll feel like
we're still together.
Are you touched?
- A little.
- Only a little?
Actually, a lot.
Maybe I should leave
something behind too.
Like what?
It's a secret. I'll tell you later.
I'll be back soon.
I'll be waiting.
DA-REUM HEART HA-GI
6 MONTHS LATER
Da-reum.
The CEO wants this version
by three o'clock.
By three o'clock today?
Yes, that's her style.
She's obviously Korean.
You can do it.
Can you?
- I can.
- Yes.
HAN AND KOREA
Finally.
Ha-gi's mission while waiting.
Sunlight.
Water, then open the window
for some sunlight.
When a new leaf grows,
send me a selfie with it.
When a bud appears,
video call and show me.
- Bye.
Bonjour.
Are you at work on the weekend?
Exactly.
Ms. Han is no joke.
She bombards me with work.
She's worse than you.
But why do you look excited?
It's tough, but it's still fun.
If you're enjoying it
even though it's tough
that means you're good at it.
You sound like a CEO.
Because I am one.
How's work? Is everything okay?
Oh, I found out just yesterday.
Mr. Young-woo and Ms. Min-a
are going out.
Really?
Oh, I knew it.
- Since when?
- Since last week.
That's crazy. How did you know?
It was obvious.
Only those two think
it's still a secret.
We were the same.
Oh, right. Check this out.
I think it's going to bloom soon.
Oh, that's so pretty.
How are you so good
at growing plants?
I always end up killing them.
- Are you grateful?
- Yes.
Give me a reward.
I miss you.
I miss you too.
Da-reum will come
to the concert on her own.
You can ride with me.
How's Seul-a going to get there?
Is she going alone?
Or should I give her a ride too?
Eyes on me.
Eyes on you.
Thank you for calling Fan Goods Shop.
Yes. The slogan?
"Take my wallet, Hun-i."
We're currently sold out.
"Min-i stole my heart"
will be available tomorrow.
You want 150? Okay.
Okay. Thank you.
Of course. It won't take long.
Bye.
One, two, three.
One, two.
- Okay.
- Nice. Good job.
REUNION OF D.N.X
IN A FULL GROUP COMEBACK
Oh, my gosh!
Now, attention!
You know what I'm going to do.
It's time.
Okay.
There's something
all new recruits must go through.
Chae-yeon, are you
Team Ha-gi or Team Chan?
Or Team Jin-sang?
- There must be at least one...
- Quiet.
I'm on Team...
Ha-gi.
You should've chosen Team Jin-sang.
She used to be on Team Ha-gi too.
- I'm on Team Young-woo now.
- I'm on Team Min-a.
Didn't I tell you not to flaunt
your office romance?
Stop it.
By the way, is Mr. Kang single?
Yes.
Separate the preferred brand data
for North America and Europe.
It looks like he's doing nothing,
but working.
Okay.
Do you want me to tell you?
Whether Mr. Kang is
in a relationship or not?
Oh, I'm sorry.
- I knew it.
- Too bad.
He already has a girlfriend.
Da-reum!
I, Nam Da-reum, just landed.
Really?
Welcome back. When did you come back?
I thought you were coming tomorrow.
I moved it up a day.
Why?
Because I missed you.
I'm finally home.
There's something
we haven't done yet.
This is it.
The reason I wanted to be back.
The manager in charge will
suggest the merchandise
in time for your comeback.
Who's the new manager?
Hello.
- Hello.
I'm your D.N.X collaboration
project manager, Nam Da-reum.
Nice to meet you.
We're honored to have you.
Then let me begin.
Your fan song "YOU" is the motive
of this collaboration.
I reflected your gratitude
to your fans for waiting so long
in the merchandise.
As you can see,
I prepared three items.
A T-shirt, a tote bag, and a cap.
You can see the details
on the T-shirt.
The pocket on the left
that's close to the heart is
embroidered with lyrics from "YOU."
That was good.
That was cool.
Oh, you're teasing me.
I mean it.
We're working together for real now.
So I'd better pull this off.
I'm not going to handle this project
as a fan.
- Then?
- As a manager
who understands the fans.
I look forward to working with you
Manager Nam Da-reum.
- Likewise, Artist Lee Chan.
- Thank you.
Good luck.
That was a good briefing.
- Did you hear it?
- I could hear your voice outside.
You sounded pretty confident.
I can leave you
with an even bigger project now.
Are you complimenting me,
so you can make me work overtime?
Not today.
- Why not?
- I have a date with my boyfriend.
THROUGH ALL TIME AND SPACE
For the lyrics,
the fans will like this...
and this the most.
Okay, Ms. Da-reum.
Then...
Is this right?
That's perfect.
D.N.X CONCERT ATTIRE REFERENCE DESIGN
CHECK COMEBACK SHOWCASE SPONSOR BOOTH
CONFIRM STAGE OUTFIT KEY MERCHANDISE
This is the hardest.
MANAGER NA WON-BIN
Yes, Mr. Na.
What?
Someone posted
a terrorist threat online.
It's likely to be a prank
but the police are going
to search the whole area.
So we had to cancel the venue.
So the place we booked in a rush is
here.
CONCERT HALL
Isn't it too small?
The stage is too close
to the audience.
So we'll have to change
the stage outfit.
- Our key merchandise too?
- Sorry about that.
I'll have to ask you to change it
according to their new stage outfit.
Announce the change of address
on all available channels.
CHANGE IN SHOWCASE VENUE
Let me check.
Show only the half
of the merchandise shelf.
Since it's invitation only,
create a registration link.
1ST D.N.X FANDOM PRESIDENT
My blood is finally pumping again.
Pay attention, D-Angels.
This is where D.N.X is performing
for real.
Check the link and run for it.
1ST D.N.X FANDOM PRESIDENT
CHECK THE LINK
THE WHOLE GROUP? FOR REAL?
I'M IN TEARS
SATURDAY, OCTOBER 3, 2026
ART LIVE HALL
Enjoy cheering.
Hello, take one.
- Enjoy cheering.
- Good luck.
Thank you.
- Hello. Take one.
- Enjoy cheering.
- Check if that's you.
- Did you make that yourself?
- Yes.
- Nice.
- That's so cool.
- Thank you.
President Kim!
I was waiting for your post!
- I read your posting.
- Really?
- Did you read my post?
- Yes.
Awesome.
Here. Take one.
- Thank you.
- We'll be cheering inside.
All right.
Lastly, you need to put
on the merchandise from Appello.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Good to see you again.
Ta-da.
That's nice.
That looks like a shooting star.
- Is that...
- Yes.
The stage is smaller.
but the fans will be happy
to get closer to you.
So I just added small details.
The closest light you can see.
Thank you
for giving this back to me.
It's time for you
to shine on stage now.
Sounds good.
Are you ready?
What about the fans? Are there many?
See it for yourself.
It's worth coming all the way here.
I get to see them in front.
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
I hope Roy does well.
I believe
in the stage genius.
The stage master!
I know Roy can do it.
Who's your favorite, Mi-mi?
I first began as Chan.
Then I became obsessed with Hyeok.
What about now?
You?
That's all that matters.
Hey!
Get a room, will you?
Today
my bias is returning to the stage.
It should be a national holiday.
Wait.
Let's go.
Okay, they waited nine years for us.
- Let's give our all.
- Okay.
- One.
- Two.
- Three.
- Four.
Five. Let's go.
- Let's go!
- Get in the picture.
- Okay.
One, two, three.
They're here!
Hyeok!
So cool!
- D.N.X!
I love them.
Well...
We weren't sure what to sing
for our first song.
But first
thank you so much for waiting for us
for all these years.
This song is...
dedicated to you and everyone...
who helped us...
get back on stage.
The title is...
"YOU."
Perhaps everything that shines
Fades away every day
Dreaming makes me feel like myself
But now,
I'm barely surviving each day
The attention that surrounds me
And waiting for the cheers
Makes me nervous
like walking on thin ice
I close my eyes and dream
- Goodnight
- Chan.
Sometimes everything brings me
Down
Only you
Only you make me feel like I exist
So cool!
When I get lost
In the world
Through all time
- And space
- Hyeok!
We'll dream together again
Only you
Make me feel like I exist
BACK AS FIVE AGAIN
D-ANGEL WILL BE WITH YOU FOREVER
SHINING STARS ON STAGE
D.N.X FOREVER
It's surprising
How time changes everything
Roy!
We were nothing at first
I once
chased after a shining star.
But what lit my path
was more than that.
Every time I thought I was alone
there was a light shining beside me.
I think I like you, Mr. Kang.
No matter how hard things get
don't let go of my hand.
But now
I know...
that stars are not far away.
All these lights are
stars emitting their own light
from where they are.
Only you
Only you make me feel like I exist
When I get lost
In the world
Through all time and space
We'll dream together again
Only you
Make me feel like I exist
The moment
I become someone's light...
I, too
start shining in my own way.
Over here.
Oh, bubbles.
Da-reum.
It's so cute.
- Do you like it?
- I love it.
Get me a ring and make it a full set.
No.
It withers soon.
But it feels good.
Get me a ring with a big flower.
Where are the flowers?
But I want to give you this.
I want
to be a place
for you to return to every day.
Will you...
stay by my side?
Yes.
I'll be by your side every day.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
SPECIAL THANKS TO PARK SEO-JIN
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
Subtitles by Eunjin Erica Kim
and Jennifer Jean Lim
Synced and corrected by
WEISSACHsubs